

## Summary

I'm Pourya Dehghan a Software engineer with the background of petrochemical engineering educations and designing experience. I started my coding journey two years ago, I feel really lucky that my job is my biggest hobby. I'm eager to make the leap and continue refining my skills with the right company.

### **Skills**

HTML, CSS JavaScript, Python React, React Native, Boostrap Django, MongoDB PostgreSQL, Github Photoshop, Lightroom

# **Education and Training**

#### Certificated

General Assembly Remote Software Engineer , 08/2021

#### Bachelor of Science

Marvdasht Azad University Petrochemical Engineer, 2013

## Languages

**English** 

Persian

Turkish

## Experience

#### General Assembly

Software Engineer | Remote 05/2021 to 08/2021

- Learning programming and computer science fundamentals, and creating full stack applications.
- Feature Projects:

**Denj**-This is a full stack mobile application that I created with React Native. This application is about cozy places that users have been and they want to share with other people.

Agora-This is the full stack application that we created as a group. This is an online application for discussions on a forum based on topics and descriptions. Each forum has their own and is fully functional.

**Dota2 Heroes-**My App is called Dota2 Heroes. It's an app that shows the all Dota2 Heroes and if you click on hero it gives you the detail and attributes of that hero.

**Dota2\_Simon-**This is a Simon game which players must repeat random sequences of by clicking the buttons in correct order. The differences between this game and the other Simon games are that I used the Dota 2 character's images and sounds to make it more interesting.

#### Uber

Driver | Atlanta, GA 04/2017 to 06/2021 Provided excellent customer service to patrons Interacted with riders.

#### Yerce

Photo Editor & Designer  $\mid$  Turkey 06/2014 to 12/2016 Photography company specializing in wedding photos and albums.

# Designed and created wedding albums for customers.

## Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.pouryadegan.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/degan90
- https://github.com/Degan90